Inventory of the Papers of Monroe Leigh, 1941 - 2001
University of Virginia, Arthur J. Morris Law Library
- Personal Papers
  - Correspondence
    - Personal Correspondence, 1981 (Box-folder 49 - 11)
      Contains signatures, handwritten notations, newspaper article photocopies, looseleaf notes, invitations, Correspondents include: G. P. Thukov, Monroe Leigh, Robert J. Corber, Geoverts O. J. Van Tets, C. Euguene Webb, Willis L. M. Reese, Paul A. Pavlis, Richard Combs, John R. Cooke, Jr., U.S. Department of Transportation, George W. Coombe, Jr., Samuel D. Engle, Michael H. Cardozo, C. Barrie Cook, Mr. and Mrs. Heribert Golsong, Edward Gordon, Toby S. Myerson, Franz M. Oppenheimer, Yale Club Library,Mr. Gerals and Mrs. Julia Draper, Louis S. Emery, John Hannaway, John Heinz, J. Howard Settle, Howard Holtzmann, Lindsey Cowen, Hart Perry, Edward Dumbauld, Philip C. Jessup, Lawrence Collins, Peter C. Manson, Malcolm R. Pfunder, John A Westberg, Malcolm R. Wilkey, Ms. Haas - Circle 8 Ranch, Joseph P. Griffin, James E. Edmunds, Mary Gardiner Jones, Robert M. Flanagan, Robert Womack, Hardy C. Dillard, Davis R. Robinson, William R. Bailey, Aron Broches, Paul J. Stadtler, William R. Bailey, Terry L. Leitzell, Department of Highways, Robert Womack, John C. Roots, Betty Esau, Ignaz Seidl-Hohenveldern, Rosalyn Higgins, Mark B. Feldman, David Schachter, Robert O. Blake, Joseph A. Greenwald, Pierce McCrary, Mrs. E. Miles Herter, John Lehman, Adele Herter Seroude, Walter J. Stoessel, Jr., John D. Epperly, John O. Marsh, Jr., Phillip R. Trimble, Jerry H. Weiss, Tariq Hassan, John Lehman, Christian A. Herter, Jr., Harold H. Saunders, Roberts B. Owen, Michael Brnadon, J. Peter A. Bernhard, Maurice D. Copithorne, Takashi Watanabe, Mason Willrich
    - Personal Correspondence, 1982 (Box-folder 50 - 1)
      Contains signatures, handwritten notations, post-it notes, article photocopies, envelopes, invitations, draft article letter responses resumes, correspondents include: Monroe Leigh, Comptroller of the Treasury - Income Tax Division, M. D. Copithorne, Richard M. Hammer, Frank W. Swacker, Juk H. van Maanen, Jerry H. Weiss, Orm Ketcham, Sidney Picker, Jr., Mustafa Sayid, Board of Directors - Hamlet Place Owners, Inc., Harry Tyson Carter, Robert B. Oakley, Byron Farwell, Virginia M. Dondy, C. Karen Troy, Aron (Ronnie) Broches, James M. Michel, Fomad? Riad?, Mr. Riddle, Kempton B. Jenkins, Walking Horse Report, Voice of the Tennessee Walking Horse, Walking Horse Report, Arthur R. Albrecht, Francis A. Boyle, Daivd A. Greenburg, William T. England, Chevy Chase Chevrolet, Elisabeth Zoller, Roland de Kergorlay, William R. Felts, Chester H. Brandon, Charles G. Williamson, Jr., Dante B. Fascell, Jacqueline A. McCard, Scott Heuer, Jr., William W. Dunn, John D. Epperly, Michio Mizoguchi, Internal Revenue Service Center, Maryland Income Tax Division, Harry W. Fawcett, Paul Brothers, Inc., Justice Lewis F. Powell, Jr., Bruno A. Ristau, Ronald S. Katz, Sam Eggleston, Jr., Arthur J. Rothkopf, Henry A. Kissinger, Kathleen Sylvester, John R. Cooke, Department of Parking and Transportation Services, J. Stewart McClendon, Peter Auery, Chevrolet Motor Division, Timothy W. Stanley, Herbert D. Spivack, R. W. Munro, Interstate Federal Savings and Loan Association, Mr. and Mrs. Joseph Prendergast, Kanenori Oshikiri, Geico
    - Personal Correspondence, 1983 (Box-folder 50 - 2)
      Contains signatures, handwritten notations, looseleaf notes, invitations, resumes, newspaper clippings, post-it notes, Correspondents include: Monroe Leigh, Gamal M. Badr, William J. Flather, III, Yukio Takeuchi, Kanenori Oshikiri, Margo Grant, David Gregg, III, Phillip I. Blumberg, Walter W. Brooks, Jr., Morris I. Leibman, Joseph E. Lombardi, Michael A. Daniels, Toby S. Myerson, Howard B. Hill, Father Joseph Snee, Craig Mathews, Franz M. Oppenheimer, George H. and Rosemary Aldrich, Dan S. Cross, John R. Stevenson, Nan Oldham, George P. Armour, Bob Jordan, Gerald and Julia Draper, Jeswald W. Salacuse, Colonial Parking, Inc., Victoria E. Marmorstein, Arthur R. Albrecht, Gustave M. Hauser, Edward G. Aldrich, Philip Kinkaid, Barbara Anderson - Flather & Hayes Company, K. Martin Worthy, Arthur W. Rovine, Guido Brosio, M. D. Cppithorne, Edward D. Re, Dean Koerth, Pascale Abdelmour, Roy Hamlin Johnson, H. James Conaway, Irene Savanis, Richard (Pokie) Edmunds, Virginia State Highway Commission, Stefan A. Riesenfeld, Werner Hein, Derek M. D. Thomas, James H. Michel, Eugene V. Rostow, Mrs. Wilson (Peggy) Anderson, W. E. Mussman, James C. Conner, Elisabeth Zoller, Julius Kaplan, Marvin J. Colangelo, John F. Murphy, R. Shuman,
    - Personal Correspendence, 1984 (Box-folder 50 - 3)
      Contains signatures, looseleaf notes, handwritten notations, newspaper clippings/photocopies, envelopes, highlights, pamphlets, Correspondents include: Hernan Felipe Errazuriz, Monroe Leigh, William J. Flather, III, George H. Aldrich, Parking and Traffic - American University, W. Richard Mason, Photoduplication Service - Library of Congress, Sidney Picker, Jr., John Hanley, Henry A. Kissinger, S. L. Gidden, Ronald A. Jacks, Brice M. Clagett, Richard Wilberforce, Peter D. Trooboff, Michael Axelrod, Marsha T. Rogers, Holly A. Nelson, Mark E. Ellis, Dante B. Fascell, Friedrich Schwank, Wally Brooks, Gillian Jones, John Ritchie, Gerald M. Finkel, Phillip I. Blumberg, William H. Berman, Heribert Golsong, Jeffrey H. Smith, Raymond J. Waldmann, Rodric Braithwaite, Hitchcock Shoes, Inc.
    - Personal Correspondence, 1994 (Box-folder 50 - 4)
      Contains signatures, photocopies, revisions, Correspondents include: Mark Warner, Monroe Leigh, Chris T. Antoniou, Henry T. King, Jr., Stuart H. Deming, Richard C. Allison, Sabine Schlemmer-Schulte, Transamerica Occidental Life Insurance Company, Ted Meron, Jennifer Schwebel, Lowell Satler, Aetna Life Insurance Co., Glenn Sedam, Liza Phillips, Budget Rent-A-Car, Roger Warin, Mary Keane, Euro-Motor, Nations Bank
    - Personal Correspondence, Jan - June 1995 (Box-folder 50 - 5)
      Contains handwritten notes, signatures, markup, post-it notes, photocopies, Correspondents include: Monroe Leigh, William H. Webster, Sir Adam Bulter DL, Alex Morrison, William C. Mott, Howell Raines, Antonio Cassese, Conrad K. Harper, Selena J. Linde, Elizabeth A. Snodgrass, Eugene H. Matthews, Frank W. Swacker, University Press of Virginia, Daniel J. Meador, Lawrence Collins, Marcia Warren, David C. Gill
    - Personal Correspondence, Aug - Dec 1995 (Box-folder 50 - 6)
      Contains handwritten notes, highlights, photocopies, transcriptions, signatures, appraisal of applicant for Georgetown University Law Center, Correspondents include: Alan K. Simpson, Edward M. Kennedy, Monroe Leigh, Timothy Clancy, David Ibbeken, Admissions Club - Cosmos Club, Fiona A. Brophy, Francisco Orrego Vicuna, Ernest C. Mead, Jr., Mr. Klemens and Mrs. Betty von Klemperer, Paul Ure, James Crawford, John Norton Moore, Albert R. Turnball, James Milligan, Jennifer Schwebel, John Wesley, Malcolm R. Wilkey, University of Virginia - Printing and Copying Services, Joseph M. Sweeney, John W. Heffernan, Hume Boggis-Rolfe, Stephen M. Schwebel, Marco C.E.J. Bronckers, Thomas J. Nicastro
    - Personal Corresopndence, Jan - June 1996 (Box-folder 50 - 7)
      Contains signatures, handwritten notes, Correspondents include: Monroe Leigh, Theodor Meron, Detlev Vagts, John J. Dugard, James Crawford, Wolfson College Cambridge Properties Limited, Charles N. Brower, Mr. John and Mrs. Barbara Moore, Roberts B. Owen, Charles M. Mathias, Marco C.E.J. Bronckers, Gerog Ress, Yuji Iwasawa, Hannah Scott, Gordon Johnson, Eli Lauterpacht, Anna Ascher, Chairman - Membership Committee - American Law Institute, Judah Best, Robert H. Craft, Jr., Sebastian Alegrett, Elliot L. Richardson, Andy Mayer, Jennifer Schwebel, Dean of Admissions - Harvard Law School, Dean of Admissions - New York University School of Law, Dean of Admissions - National Law Center - The George Washington University, Dean of Admissions - The Washington College of Law - The American University, Dean of Admissions - Vanderbilt University - School of Law, Louis Henkin, Thomas M. Franck, Louis Sohn, Robert K. Goldman, Jonathan Charney, Edith Brown-Weiss, John N. Moore, Dean of Admissions - College of Arts and Sciences - University of Virginia
    - Personal Correspondence, Aug - Dec 1996 (Box-folder 51 - 1)
      Contains signatures, handwritten notes, notifications, Correspondents include: Monroe Leigh, Rollin Amore, Theodor Meron, Detlev Vagts, Charles Brower, Walter and Sara - Wolfson College, Lise - Hewlett-Packard, Professor J. Dugard, Andrew C. Mayer - Woflson College, Helene Cohen - The American Law Institute, Branch Manager - Citicorp, George C. Freeman, Visa First Card, Geico - Auto Insurance Renewal Questionnaire, David, Elizabeth F. Leigh, Auto Rental Insurance, Ms. Snyder, Department of Financial Services - County of Loudoun, Hower Bowie, Lawrence Collins, Marco C.E.J. Bronckers, Edward M. Leigh, Jr., G. E. Capital Insurance Services Group, Al Rubin, Delta Skymiles Center, Kevin Olivera, Howard E. Hensleigh, Richard Lillich, Maija S. Blauberga
    - Personal Correspondence, Jan - March 1997 (Box-folder 51 - 2)
      Contains signatures, newspaper photocopies, Correspondents include: Monroe Leigh, Dr. A. Vaughan and Sally Lowe, Fadi Makki, Jack L. Goldsmith, Lord Richard Wilberforce, Denis Dejersey-Lowney, Rolan Amore, Thomas N. Connally, Jennifer Raney, Mary Druce, Carol Rhees, Paul H. Dulaney, Jr., James E. Edmunds, Brussells Family, Theodor Meron, Wolfson College, Edward M. Leigh, Jr., Thomas P. Nigra, Mrs. Glen Howard, Henry McFarland, Malcolm N. Shaw, Frank Dawson, Clive DuVal, Social Security Administration, Treasurer - Loudoun County, Paul Lovejoy, Marion Barry, Catherine Kessedjian, John Dugard, James Crawford, Cambridge Friends of Development Office, VISA World Access Service Corporation, GE Capital Insurance Services Group, Charlene Barshefsky, Frank Griffith Dawson, Clint N. Smith, State Street Bank & Trust Company
    - Personal Correspondence, April - Dec 1997 (Box-folder 51 - 3)
      Contains signatures, newspaper photocopies, tax and revenue information, handwritten notes, registration photocopies, Who's Who in America photocopy, Correspondents include: Madeline K. Albright, Monroe Leigh, Mary Leigh, Edward M. Leigh, Jr., The New York Review of Books, Moore, Clemens & Co., Inc., Roland Amore, Todd Kern, Charles Jones, Stephen M. Schwebel, Harry G. Barnes, Jr., Eli Lauterpacht, Department of Financial Services - County of Loudoun, John F. Murphy, Bob Jones, Ted Meron, Virginia G. Watkin, The Admissions Committee - Cosmos Club, Patrick Coyne, Roy Hamlin Johnson, Time Life Books, Mileage Plus First Card, Jennifer L. Krieger, Hertz International, Forte-Agip Hotel, Eleanor D. Acheson, Shara L. Aranoff, Dr. A. Vaughn and Mrs. Sally Lowe, Michael Scharf, Jeremy P. Carver, Lord and Lady Wilberforce, Julia Draper, Patricia McGinnis, David T. Link, Thomas D. Grant, Barbara Stone, Cairo Robb, Raymond Shafer, Gianni Manca, Andrew C. Mayer, Amerigas, Misha Meijers, Calvin H. Cobb, Jr., Meineke Hotel, Verena Weinstabl, Christopher R. Wall, Secretary - Board of Governors - Metropolitan Club, Michael D. Sandler, Thelma Guerra, Dr. h. c. M. Necati Munir Ertekun, Jessica T. Matthews, Denis Dejersey-Lowney, Francisco Orrego Vicuna, John Waters, Douglass C. Crummett, Christian R. Bartholomew, Christina M. Deane, Jonathan M .Beart, Leslie Douglas, John Shattuck, Brice Clagett, Heffers Booksellers, Jane Edmonds Penner, Ernest C. Mead, Jr, M. Cherif Bassiouni, Cally Jordan, William Fugate, Ian Brownlie, James Crawford, William D. Denson, Mr. Hillen, Jennifer Raney, Charles Maechling, Jr.,
    - Personal Correspondence, 1998 (Box-folder 51 - 4)
      Contains signatures, newspaper photocopies, Correspondents include: Frank Sieverts, Monroe Leigh, Mrs. William D. [Huschi] Denson, Constance A. Morella, Lord Richard Wilbeforce, Edwin Williamson, Charles L. McCormick, III, James [Jimmie] and Sylvia Symington, E. Ralph Coon, Jr., Malcolm R. Wilkey, The Washington Institute of Foreign Affairs, F.L.P. [Peter] and Jeanne White, Edward M. Leigh, Jr., Charles Jones, Edgar A. Prichard, Thomas N. Connally, Rollin Amore, Lawrence S. Eagleburger, Bartram S. Brown, Robert Scott, Secretary - Board of Governors - Chevy Chase Club, James E. Edmunds, Jennifer Raney, Michael C. G. Dunner, Yuji Iwasawa, Henry A. Kissinger, Nicholas Grace, William Brewer, Sara Marley, Tedson J. Meyers, Admissions Committee - Cosmos Club, Charles Jones, Moore Clemens & Company, Inc., Jack Chorowsky, Alexander Leigh
  - University of Virginia Law School Seminar
    - Legal Problems of International Trade, 1964 (Box-folder 51 - 5)
      Sensitive material - Grades, contains roster (handwritten) with attendance, course materials and outlines, correspondence, looseleaf notes, handwritten notations, 13 students including R. P. Borsody, D. F. Carlson, W. M. Dickey, B. H. Hill, E. P. Humann, R. W. Klein, B. L. Lau, W. P. Maloney, J. T. Martin, R. Minshall, J. H. Riggs, R. K. Rudolph, Meemmery, Correspondents include: Edward A. Mearns, Jr., Monroe Leigh, Hardy C. Dillard, Virginia Haith, N. Thompson Powers, John Rehm, L. H. Rhinelander, Christopher A. Leventis, Frances Farmer, Lindsey Cowen, Paul J. Jenkins, Weldon Cooper, Edgar F. Shannon, Jr.
    - Legal Problems of Foreign Trade, 1965 (Box-folder 51 - 6)
      Contains roster (handwritten) with attendance, course materials and outlines, correspondence, looseleaf notes, newspaper clippings, handwritten notations, 12 students including Beard, Bruce, Crawford, Garofalo, Haskell, Hemschoot, Lamberton, Logan, McAllister, Piassick, Raiser, Ranom, Correspondents include: The West Publishing Company, C. Victor Raiser, II, Paul J. Hemschoot, Jr., Claude Crawford, Virginia Haigh, W. Robert Beard, Galbreath E. Palmer, Richard E. Speidel, Hardy C. Dillard, Mason Willrich, Frances Farmer, Roger F. Noreen, Peter W. Low, Edgar F. Shannon, Jr., Thomas S. Currier, Bevin Alexander, Murray Belman, L. H. Rhinelander, Izaak Glasser, Edward A. Mearns, Jr.,
    - Legal Problems of Foreign Trade, 1966 (Box-folder 51 - 7)
      Sensitive material - Grades, Contains roster (handwritten) with attendance, course materials and outlines, handwritten notations, correspondence, 7 students including Deddish, Haith, Hsia, Kennedy, Lang, Perce, Hausen, Correspondents include: Charles R. Titus, Monroe Leigh, Mason Willrich, Robert H. Knight, Murray Belman, Robert Perce, Frank L. Hereford, Jr., Hardy C. Dillard, Michael R. Deddish, Jr., James C. Conner
    - Legal Problems of International Trade, 1967 (Box-folder 51 - 8)
      contains roster (handwritten) with attendance, correspondence, course materials and outlines, handwritten notations, 12 students including R. E. Bresler, G. G. Davis, R. S. Davis, D. M. DeWilde, S. S. Dye, D. S. Fitzpatrick, W. P. Macht, G. Palmer, G. K. Stewart, M. Sullivan, F. T. Tuttle, T. C. Williams, correspondents include: Frances Farmer, Monroe Leigh, Hardy C. Dillard, Virginia Haigh, David M. DeWilde, Murray Belman, Peter Manson, Robert S. Davis, Carrol D. Hammer, William P. Macht, Stuart S. Dye, D. S. Fitzpatrick, G. G. Davis, G. Palmer, R. F. Loving, William E. Miller, David E. Plymire, Peter W. Low
    - Legal Problems of International Trade, 1968 (Box-folder 52 - 1)
      Sensitive material - Grades, contains roster (handwritten) with attendance, correspondence, course materials and outlines, handwritten notations, newspaper clippings, looseleaf notes, 13 students including G. D. Best, Ralph C. Bresler, S. W. Faber, L. Goetz, J. S. Hannon, W. W. Kirtley, E. A. Kratovil, S. Lengthaisong, J. D. Mollica, W. R. Pearson, W. Taylor Reveley, III, K. T. Watson, Sheppard, Correspondents include: Monroe Leigh, Taylor Reveley, III, Virginia Haigh, Ralph C. Bresler, Murray J. Belman, James Evans, William H. Weiland, Mason Willrich, David E. Plymire, G. D. Best, Peter C. Manson, Board Head Inn, William E. Miller, R. F. Loving, James C. Conner, James G. Evans, Jr., Frances Farmer, Peter Low, Frank L. Hereford, Jr.,
    - Legal Problems of International Trade, 1969 (Box-folder 52 - 2)
      Sensitive Material - Grades, contains roster with attendance, correspondence, course materials and outlines, handwritten notations, looseleaf notes, 9 students including W. J. Beerworth, M. R. Bromley, H. E. Jennings, J. L. McDougal, Miss Susan M. Sharpley, Randolph W. Urmston, William H. Weiland, Maj. Stanley J. Glod, P. T. Zieman, Correspondents include: Monroe Leigh, H. Lane Kneedler, Virginia Haigh, Roy G. Bowman, Alexandre Kafka, Susan Sharpley, Jan Chowaniec, R. F. Loving, Randolph W. Urmston, William H. Weiland, Shelby J. Conley, John Rhinelander, Harry E. Jennings, Jr., Hazel Key, William C. Hill, Farmington Country Club, William E. Miller, Frances Farmer, Jerome Stone, Peter W. Low, Little Brown and Company, Maj. Stanley J. Glod, Mason Willrich, Frank L. Hereford, Jr., Monrad G. Paulsen, Hardy C. Dillard
    - Legal Problems of International Trade, 1970 (Box-folder 52 - 3)
      Contains roster with attendance, correspondence, course materials and outlines, handwritten notations, 9 students including R. M. Glenn, W. H. Heritage, L. E. Leonoff, S. B. MacDonald, Alastair K. Maxwell, Marshall V. Miller, J. A. Mullins, J. M. Naboco, R. C. White, Correspondents include Virginia Haigh, S. B. MacDonald, Alastair K. Maxwell, Marshall V. Miller, Frances Farmer, William G. Christopher, H. Lane Kneedler, Monrad G. Paulsen, Peter C. Manson
    - Legal Problems of International Trade, 1971 (Box-folder 52 - 4)
      Contains roster with attendance, correspondence, newspaper clippings, looseleaf notes, course materials and outlines, handwritten notations, 12 students including Beninati, Boswell, Cowles, Gearhart, Harper, Holland, Lemmer, Macleod, John A. McVickar, L. Thomas Galloway, Nicklin, Correspondents include: Virginia Haigh, Monroe Leigh, L. Thomas Galloway, William D. Broderick, John A. McVickar, William V. Lawson, Robert D. Wallick, William E. Miller, Alice Crane, The Colonnade Club, H. Lane Kneedler, The Dean's Office, Monrad G. Paulsen
    - Legal Problems of International Trade, 1972 (Box-folder 52 - 5)
      Contains roster with attendance, course materials and outlines, correspondence, looseleaf notes, handwritten notations, 9 students including Capt. Royal Daniel, Col. John Jay Douglass, Dennis Fenwick, David Goodman, Roger H. Hull, Louis Verbeke, John Hardin Young, Leonard L. McCants, Mrs. Dulcey Fowler, Correspondents include: John H. Young, Monroe Leigh, Roger H. Hull, Stanley D. Metzger, Virginia Haigh, Leonard L. McCants, Charles Runyon, III, Col. John Jay Douglass, Capt. Royal Daniel, Louis Verbeke, Frances Farmer, Alexandre Kafka, Monrad G. Paulsen
    - Legal Problems of International Trade, 1973 (Box-folder 52 - 6)
      Contains roster with attendance, course materials and outlines, correspondence, looseleaf notes, handwritten notations, newspaper clippings, 7 students including Margaret Ashby, P. B. Fitzpatrick, J. E. Hadley, David Patton Parker, A. Pillet, John M. Skonberg, Patrick Vaghi, Correspondents include: John Skonberg, Monroe Leigh, Virginia Haigh, Frank G. Robertson, H. Lane Kneedler, J. Dapray Muir, J. E. Hadley, Paul P. Streeten, David Patton Parker, Alice Crane, William E. Miller, J. M. Skonberg, R. F. Loving, S. Margeton, B. Esau, Margaret S. Taylor, Monrad G. Paulsen
    - Legal Problems of International Trade, 1974 (Box-folder 52 - 7)
      Sensitive material - Grades, Contains roster with attendance, course materials and outlines, correspondence, looseleaf notes, handwritten notations, 7 students including Barry, Halkyard, Raymond Hanzlik, Kyld, Wayne Smith, Whitman, Richard de Wilde, correspondents include: Virginia Haigh, Richard (Dick) de Wilde, Murray J. Belman, H. Lane Kneedler, Betty Esaue, Monroe Leigh, Farmington Country Club attn: Alice Crane, William E. Miller, Mary Frye, Frances Farmer, Henry C. Ikenberry, Richard Frank, Rayburn Hanzlik, Alexandre Kafka, R. F. Loving, Mrs. Barnett, Marian R. Macbeth, Ray C. Hunt, Jr., Monrad G. Paulsen
    - Legal Problems of International Trade, 1975 (Box-folder 52 - 8)
      Contains memos, course materials and outlines, Correspondents include Monrad Paulsen, Morton Pomeranz, Monroe Leigh, Mr. Mickey, Mr. Cunningham, Mr. Plaine, Timothy Atkeson, H. Lane Kneedler, Chester R. Titus
    - International Trade, 1978 (Box-folder 52 - 9)
      Sensitive material - Grades, taught with Royal Daniel, correspondence, roster with attendance, memos, course materials and outlines, looseleaf notes, handwritten notations, 12 students including Ann Marie Anawaty, Robert Arkin, Debra Bowen, David Brown, M. C. Cramer, Daniel Duval, Patrick Hamilton, Helen Kelley, Randall Kirk, Vicki Marmostein, Kenneth Peoples, Henry Stopford, Correspondents include: Royal Daniel, Monroe Leigh, Richard B. Lillich, Virginia Haigh, Vicki E. Marmorstein, Debra L. Bowen, Daniel Duval, Carole Smith, David S. Brown, Jon Hines, Lane Kneedler, Robert D. Arkin, Betty Esau, Philip Stopford, Henry C. Ikenberry, Alice Crane, Colonnade Club, Chester R. Titus, Larry B. Wenger
    - International Trade, 1979 (Box-folder 53 - 1)
      Sensitive material - Grades, taught with Alexandre Kafka, Contains Harvard Law School pamphlet and letter re: Functions and Procedures of the Visiting Committees (1975 - 76), photocopies, articles, roster with attendance, correspondence, memos, course materials and outlines, evaluations, envelopes, looseleaf notes, handwritten notations, 13 students including Anthony Anderson, Wild Chang, G. Rich Eiselt, Peter Hartog, Frances Henderson, Orlan Lee, Tom McDonald, Bryan Parker, Daniel Rhoads, Gilles Sion, Charles Tribbett, Tim Woodhouse, Douglas Woodworth, Correspondents include: Monroe Leigh, Detlev F. Vagts, Peter Hartog, Alexandre Kafka, Dean Spies, Robert Lillich, Paul Johnson, Betty Esau, H. Lane Kneedler, Virginia Haigh, Orlan Lee, Douglas C. Woodworth, Mary Jo White, Gilles Sion, Royal Daniel, Debra L. Bowen, Larry B. Wenger, Carole Smith, Colonnade Club, West Publishing Company
    - International Trade, 1980 (Box-folder 53 - 2)
      Sensitive material - Grades, taught with Alexandre Kafka, Contains roster with attendance, memos, course materials and outlines, signatures, handwritten notations, correspondence with faculty and students, looseleaf notes, 11 Students including: Ziad A. Al-Sudairy, David J. Carol, Jon P. Cramer, Milan Ganik, Michael M. Gondwe, Jo Ann Miles, Frederic C. Rich, Dennis Bisong Tambe, W. Gary Vause, Roger B. Wagner, Daniel Zavala, Correspondents include: Monroe Leigh, Hugh Smith, Virginia Haigh, Lane Kneedler, David Carol, Milan Ganik, Law Council, Elizabeth Lowe, Jo Ann Miles, Roger Wagner, Colonnade Club, Daniel Zavala
    - International Trade, 1981 (Box-folder 53 - 3)
      Offered Spring 1981 with Alexandre Kafka of the IMF, Contains memos, course planning materials, handwritten notes, Correspondents include: Monroe Leigh, Alexandre Kafka, Elizabeth B. Lowe, Lane Kneedler, Royal Daniel, Bettie Hall
    - International Trade, 1982 (Box-folder 53 - 4)
      Sensitive material - Grades, Contains memos, roster with attendance, course materials and outlines, signatures, handwritten notations, looseleaf notes, evaluations, envelopes, correspondence with faculty and students, newspaper articles photocopies, 13 students including: Ellen Cone, Jim Croker, Michael Dalton, Hazen Dempster, Joyce Elden, Amelia C. Fawcett, Edmond M. Ianni, Ken Lee, Wendell Maddrey, Richard P. Merski, Elizabeth Springer, D. Karen Troy, Peter Adler, Correspondents include: Elizabeth B. Lowe, Lane Kneedler, Monroe Leigh, Paul Stephan, Ed Ianni, S. S. Reddy, Virginia Haigh, Kenneth Lee, Hazen H. Dempster, Richard Merski, Carole Milks, Alexandre Kafka, Bettie H. Hall, John H. Jackson
  - University of Virginia Student Materials